[
    {
      "question": "36 \u00f7 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "choices": [
        "-1",
        "0",
        "1",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "92 - 14 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "78",
      "choices": [
        "74",
        "75",
        "78",
        "80",
        "83"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "30 \u00f7 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "choices": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "5",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "74 - 29 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "45",
      "choices": [
        "40",
        "42",
        "45",
        "48",
        "50"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "60",
      "choices": [
        "57",
        "59",
        "60",
        "61",
        "63"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 48 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "112",
      "choices": [
        "108",
        "111",
        "112",
        "114",
        "116"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 93 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "128",
      "choices": [
        "124",
        "125",
        "128",
        "132",
        "133"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "38 - 12 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "choices": [
        "21",
        "24",
        "26",
        "29",
        "30"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 47 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "99",
      "choices": [
        "95",
        "96",
        "97",
        "99",
        "103"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 21 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "93",
      "choices": [
        "91",
        "92",
        "93",
        "94",
        "97"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 36 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "114",
      "choices": [
        "110",
        "111",
        "114",
        "117",
        "118"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 39 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "108",
      "choices": [
        "104",
        "106",
        "108",
        "109",
        "112"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "80 - 24 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "choices": [
        "53",
        "54",
        "56",
        "58",
        "61"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 77 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "108",
      "choices": [
        "104",
        "105",
        "107",
        "108",
        "113"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "95 - 58 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "choices": [
        "32",
        "33",
        "35",
        "36",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 45 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "142",
      "choices": [
        "138",
        "140",
        "142",
        "145",
        "147"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 \u00f7 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "choices": [
        "-3",
        "-2",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "48 - 16 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "choices": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "32",
        "35",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 \u00f7 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "choices": [
        "-2",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "36 \u00f7 3 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "choices": [
        "8",
        "12",
        "13",
        "16",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 42 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "112",
      "choices": [
        "110",
        "112",
        "113",
        "114",
        "117"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 28 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "57",
      "choices": [
        "52",
        "53",
        "54",
        "57",
        "62"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "87 - 53 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "choices": [
        "30",
        "32",
        "34",
        "35",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 36 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "135",
      "choices": [
        "130",
        "134",
        "135",
        "137",
        "140"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 49 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "141",
      "choices": [
        "137",
        "139",
        "140",
        "141",
        "145"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "choices": [
        "38",
        "39",
        "40",
        "42",
        "43"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "28 - 26 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "choices": [
        "-3",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 93 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "158",
      "choices": [
        "154",
        "158",
        "159",
        "162",
        "163"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "50 - 18 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "choices": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "31",
        "32",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "25 - 14 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "11",
        "13",
        "14",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "76 - 32 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "choices": [
        "41",
        "42",
        "44",
        "46",
        "47"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "72",
      "choices": [
        "69",
        "72",
        "74",
        "75",
        "77"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "34 - 31 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "choices": [
        "0",
        "2",
        "3",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 51 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "80",
      "choices": [
        "77",
        "78",
        "80",
        "81",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "choices": [
        "35",
        "40",
        "41",
        "42",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 73 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "123",
      "choices": [
        "119",
        "122",
        "123",
        "124",
        "128"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "86 - 80 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "choices": [
        "2",
        "5",
        "6",
        "7",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "82 - 64 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "choices": [
        "13",
        "15",
        "17",
        "18",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6 \u00f7 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "choices": [
        "-2",
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 7 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "14",
        "15",
        "18",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "120 \u00f7 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "choices": [
        "12",
        "14",
        "15",
        "16",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "40 \u00f7 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "choices": [
        "6",
        "9",
        "10",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "choices": [
        "32",
        "33",
        "35",
        "36",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 70 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "91",
      "choices": [
        "86",
        "90",
        "91",
        "93",
        "95"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 15 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "choices": [
        "21",
        "23",
        "25",
        "27",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "54 \u00f7 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 27 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "86",
      "choices": [
        "81",
        "84",
        "86",
        "87",
        "90"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 5 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "choices": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "11",
        "13",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "25 - 25 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "-3",
        "0",
        "1",
        "3",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "47 - 38 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 \u00f7 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "choices": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 11 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "132",
      "choices": [
        "128",
        "132",
        "133",
        "134",
        "136"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 34 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "54",
      "choices": [
        "49",
        "51",
        "52",
        "54",
        "57"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "50 - 20 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "choices": [
        "26",
        "29",
        "30",
        "32",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 67 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "163",
      "choices": [
        "161",
        "162",
        "163",
        "165",
        "166"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 \u00f7 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "choices": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "32 \u00f7 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "choices": [
        "3",
        "6",
        "8",
        "9",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6 \u00f7 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "choices": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 74 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "168",
      "choices": [
        "165",
        "168",
        "169",
        "172",
        "173"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "110",
      "choices": [
        "108",
        "109",
        "110",
        "111",
        "112"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "choices": [
        "3",
        "6",
        "8",
        "10",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "choices": [
        "31",
        "34",
        "36",
        "38",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "55 \u00f7 5 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "choices": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "11",
        "12",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "choices": [
        "13",
        "16",
        "18",
        "22",
        "23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "120 \u00f7 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "12",
        "14",
        "17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 \u00f7 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "choices": [
        "3",
        "5",
        "7",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 11 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "33",
      "choices": [
        "29",
        "31",
        "33",
        "35",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "54 \u00f7 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "choices": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "10",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "30 - 26 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "choices": [
        "-1",
        "1",
        "3",
        "4",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "81 - 64 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "choices": [
        "15",
        "17",
        "18",
        "19",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 - 12 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "10",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "99 \u00f7 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "14",
        "15",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "50 \u00f7 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "choices": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "5",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 91 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "152",
      "choices": [
        "147",
        "151",
        "152",
        "154",
        "157"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "75 - 19 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "choices": [
        "51",
        "52",
        "56",
        "59",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "36 \u00f7 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "choices": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "11",
        "13",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "choices": [
        "25",
        "27",
        "28",
        "30",
        "32"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 17 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "choices": [
        "61",
        "62",
        "65",
        "66",
        "69"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "choices": [
        "10",
        "13",
        "14",
        "16",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "92 - 41 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "51",
      "choices": [
        "46",
        "51",
        "52",
        "53",
        "54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "31 - 21 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "choices": [
        "7",
        "9",
        "10",
        "14",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "90 \u00f7 10 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "choices": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 15 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "66",
      "choices": [
        "62",
        "64",
        "66",
        "69",
        "71"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 86 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "173",
      "choices": [
        "168",
        "169",
        "171",
        "173",
        "177"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 50 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "136",
      "choices": [
        "132",
        "136",
        "138",
        "139",
        "141"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 \u00f7 7 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "choices": [
        "-2",
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 23 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "92",
      "choices": [
        "89",
        "90",
        "92",
        "94",
        "96"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "choices": [
        "1",
        "4",
        "6",
        "7",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "28 - 27 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "-4",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "45 \u00f7 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "choices": [
        "0",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "60 - 58 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "choices": [
        "-3",
        "-1",
        "2",
        "4",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 5 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "choices": [
        "35",
        "36",
        "39",
        "40",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "36 \u00f7 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "choices": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 74 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "129",
      "choices": [
        "124",
        "126",
        "128",
        "129",
        "133"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "choices": [
        "31",
        "32",
        "33",
        "36",
        "38"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 33 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "106",
      "choices": [
        "105",
        "106",
        "108",
        "109",
        "111"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 8 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "choices": [
        "28",
        "29",
        "32",
        "34",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "72",
      "choices": [
        "69",
        "70",
        "72",
        "74",
        "77"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "48 \u00f7 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "choices": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "6",
        "8",
        "12"
      ]
    }
  ]